饥渴 一位诗人曾说
Hunger, a poet once said,
是我们所知最重要的事
is the most important thing we know,
也是我们所学的第一堂课
the first lesson we learn.
但是饥渴容易被平复 容易被满足
But hunger can be easily quieted down, easily satiated.
世上存在着另外一种力量 它算是一种特殊的饥渴
There is another force, a different type of hunger,
它难以遏制 无法磨灭
an unquenchable thirst that cannot be extinguished.
它的存在造就了我们 我们才能称为“人”
It's very existence is what defines us, what makes us human.
这种力量就是 爱
That force is love.
二月8号 初始夜
各位旅客 我是本次航班的机长
Folks, this is your captain up in the flight deck.
我们将准时降落终点纽约机场
We are on our final descent into New York for an on-time arrival.
感谢您乘坐里吉斯航空
We want to thank you for flying Regis Air
如果您需要转机口的信息
and encourage that you ask us
欢迎各位乘客询问机组人员
any connecting gate information you may need.
机外此时为多云天气
We're looking at partly cloudy skies
着陆时可能会受到轻微的气流影响
and we may hit a little turbulence on our approach.
别再来了
Not again.
喂
Yes?
罗斯 来后舱一下
Rose get back here now.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
我们准备降落呢 等会吧
We're landing, whatever it is can wait.
现在来 马上来
Now. Come now!
好的好的 别激动
All right, relax.
先生 我们准备降落
Sir, we're landing.
请您关掉您的设备
Would you power off your device?
你把它叫做设备么
You call this a device?
请您关掉它
You have to turn it off.
就像警察把汽车称作车辆
It's like when a cop calls a car a "Vehicle".
或是叫你先生的时候 其实是想说你是个混蛋
Or when he calls you sir when he means "Asshole".
我在纽约有场演出
Having a little gig in New York coming up.
你再给我三四瓶伏特加
You give me three or four of those little baby vodkas
我就给你前排的座位票
I'll get you a front-row seat.
关掉它 座位调正
Turn it off, put your seat up.
我们马上要降落了 先生
We're landing, sir.
女士
Ma'am.
请将座位调正
Seat backs in the upright position.
终于到了
Finally.
机组人员注意 飞机准备着陆
Flight attendants, prepare for landing.
什么
我们要降落了吗
是的 甜心
你真是个勇敢的女孩
来 这给你
谢谢
不用谢
现在先把你的音乐关掉 我们要降落了
在此代表本次航班所有机组人员
On behalf of the cabin crew,
我想告知各位
I want to take a moment to say...
彼得 你后舱都没有好好整理么
Peter, you haven't done anything back here!
这地方乱糟糟的
This place is a mess!
-飞机上有东西 -什么意思
- There's something in the plane. - What do you mean?
-有个生物在货仓里 -嘘嘘
- Something alive in the cargo hold! - Shh-shh!
和我们一起乘坐本次航班的黑铂金奖成员
We'd like to extend a special thank you
我们表示由衷的谢意
to any Black Platinum Award mbers flying with us tonight
同时也欢迎所有乘客
and encourage all our passengers...
你到底什么意思 是狗吗
What the hell do you mean, like a dog?
不是 是一种特别特别大的生物
No, it's something really, really big.
我听到他在动
I heard it move.
地板下有撞击声
A thumping underneath the floor.
我听到了
I heard it...
彼得 货物舱单上并未列有动物
No, Peter, there are no animals on the manifest.
它想打开门闩
It tried to open the latch.
我听到声音了
I heard a noise.
然后它就走了
Then it moved away.
但是你能感觉它在动
But you can feel it moving.
请机组人员准备降落
Flight crew prepare for arrival.
你看到了吗
Did you see it?
什么都没有 我觉得你在
Nothing. I just think that you were...
哦天啊
Oh my God!
快去报告雷德芬机长
Go tell Captain Redfern!
让他提醒地面人员
Tell him to warn the landing crew!
启动紧急预案
And get emergency services!
有东西在下面
There's someone down there!
它要出来了
It's gonna give!
D航空347次航班 可以使用F滑行道
Private Delta 3-4-7, you're clear for taxiway Foxtrot.
Private Delta 3-4-7, clear for taxiway Foxtrot.
里吉斯航空753次航班 这里是肯尼迪机场
Regis Air 7-5-3, this is Kennedy ground.
Regis Air 7-5-3, Kennedy ground.
里吉斯航空753次航班 这里是肯尼迪机场 请回话
Regis 7-5-3, Kennedy ground, over.
搞什么
What the... ?
毕舍普
Bishop...
柏林起飞的里吉斯航空
a Regis Air flight out of Berlin,
767宽体客机
the 767 widebody,
停在了修护停机坪上
stopped on the service apron.
它停在哪儿做什么
What's it doing there?
停机坪已经荒废了
Apron's dead.
那里是不受保护的
That's a blind spot.
我不知道
I don't know.
那架飞机没有回应
The plane just went dark,
完全没有任何消息
shut down, flat-out quit.
没有光 没有电波 什么都没有
No lights, no radio, no nothing.
里吉斯航空753次航班 这里是肯尼迪机场 请回话
Regis 7-5-3, Kennedy ground, over.
Regis 7-5-3- Kennedy ground, please respond, over.
关闭F滑行道
Okay, shut down Foxtrot.
清空所有登机口 要求其他飞机改航
Clear all the gates and advise reroute.
机上有多少乘客
How many aboard?
几乎满员
Almost full flight, sir.
乘客 机组人员 大约210人
Passengers, crew, about 210 souls.
上帝
Holy Jesus.
我们不应该先等警察来吗 先生
Shouldn't we wait for first responders, sir?
毕舍普
Bishop?
毕舍普 等等
Bishop, wait!
引擎关了
Engines are shut down.
没有光
No lights.
哇 真冷
Whoa, it's cold.
像死尸一样
It's like a dead animal.
这里很蹊跷
There's something really wrong here.
似乎这架飞机从未起飞过一样
It's like it never moved.
从这里看比
This looks so much bigger
从屏幕上看大多了
from the ground than on the screen.
就像一个带翅膀的建筑物一样
I mean, they're like buildings with wings.
所有的遮光板都关着 看到了吗
All the window shades are shut, see that?
毕舍普
Bishop!
伙计们
Hey, fellas.
毕舍普
Bishop...
有一扇开着
Not all of them...
翻译：Rubens 冬可可 Jophy 香蕉奶昔 金刚妹 小南
召集所有应急车辆到F滑行道上来
Scramble all emergency vehicles to taxiway Foxtrot.
校对：Jophy
包括特警队和国土安全部么
SWAT, Homeland Security?
港务局 联邦调查局 运输安全局和疾控中心
Port Authority, FBI, TSA, CDC.
罗比 地面塔台上所有人都不许打电话
Robbie, no one on the tower calls home.
全面封锁消息
No one shares the news.
情况很糟 大事不妙
This is bad, real bad.
后期：hhjie     时间轴：阿黎     总监：Jophy
这架飞机上应该是无人生还了
We've got ourselves a dead airplane.
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
官方合作贴吧：百度《美剧血族》吧
百度《美剧血族》吧
血族
第一季  第一集
皇后区8阿里 托斯33街
嘿 哥们儿 你不能停在这 这有个防火栓
Hey, buddy, you can't park there. There's a fire hydrant.
医疗紧急情况
It's a medical emergency.
是吗
Oh, is it really?
如果我系不好我的领带那就是了
It will be if I can't get this tie on right.
你知道怎么系吗
You know how to tie this?
不知道 我带卡夹式的领带
I don't know, man, I wear a clip-on.
你自己搞定吧
You're on your own.
你在等人吗
You waiting for somebody?
是的 怎么了
Yeah, why?
那我需要你帮我个忙
Here's what I need you to do.
交警要是来了
The meter maid comes by,
你就跟她说这是疾控中心在处理公事 好吗
you tell them it's official CDC business, okay?
好的
Yeah, sure thing.
扎克
Zach.
嗨
Hey, man.
老兄
Hey, dude.
你迟到了
You're late.
5分钟而已 我也没办法
Five minutes. It can't be helped.
是十分钟 爸爸
Ten, Dad.
十分钟吗 好吧
Ten? Okay.
你系错了
That's wrong.
也许 也许是十分钟吧
Maybe... maybe ten.
我有种很好的预感
I got a good feeling about this.
祝我们好运
Wish us luck.
好运
Good luck.
迟到5分钟
Five minutes.
我知道 我知道了 对不起
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
是十分钟
Ten.
我给你发了五次短信
I texted you five times.
我没看到 我开车
I wouldn't have gotten that
从不看短信
'cause I don't text when I drive.
这样不安全
It's not safe.
古德温泽博士
Dr. Goodweather...
叫我伊弗就好
Eph, please.
你叫她凯莉 叫我儿子扎克
She gets Kelly, my son gets Zach,
所以叫我伊弗雷姆或者伊弗就行
so Ephraim or Eph, please.
古德温泽博士 这是法院指定的六次
Dr. Goodweather, this is the last of six
抚养权咨询会议的最后一次
court-appointed custody counselling sessions.
你四次都迟到了
You've been late for four of them.
你是想说我是因为不想来所以才迟到的吗
Are you gonna say that I'm late because I don't want to be here?
你也许有点想法 但是我真的有合理的原因
You might be onto something but I have a really good reason.
字母城幼儿园
There was this outbreak of Hantavirus
爆发了汉坦病毒
in this alphabet city pre-school.
这在北部和东部是极其罕见的
Which is extremely rare this far north and east.
古德温泽博士 你每次来
Dr. Goodweather, every time you come in
都要掌握话语权
you take over the session.
因为我是控制狂 我知道
Because I have control issues, I know.
但是我必须为自己辩解
But I have to defend myself here.
因为也许这是我最后一次机会
Because this might be my last chance.
关于这个问题我想了很久
And I've thought long and hard about this.
看来你俩潜移默化的把我
And it seems like you two have created this narrative
当成了坏人
wherein I'm the bad guy.
但是为什么
But why?
因为我不想离婚
Because I don't want out of my marriage.
我只是想让事情回到原来的样子
'Cause I want things back the way they were.
这件事不止是只涉及到你一个人 伊弗
But this isn't just about you, Eph,
也不是你想怎样就怎样的问题
what you want, not anymore.
我是流行病学家
I'm an epidemiologist.
如果我休假跑去钓鱼 会死人的
You know, if I take time off, if I go fly-fishing, people die.
我知道你工作很重要 伊弗雷姆
I get that you have an important job, Ephraim.
你在你的工作领域十分出色
And you're great at your job.
简直可以得满分
You get straight 'A's at your job.
但是我在婚姻里表现不及格 对吗
But I'm flunking our marriage, is that it?
你在写什么 别写了
What are you writing? Please stop writing.
我到底有多差
How horrible am I?
你并不差
You're not horrible.
你只是不着家
You're just barely present.
我为了让你回来
I've done everything you've asked me to
已经做了所有你要我做的事
in order to get us back together again.
我戒了酒
I quit drinking.
你想一个人呆着 所以我搬出去住
You wanted time alone so I moved out,
尽管我本人并不想
against my own wishes.
我对你言听计从
I've jumped through every hoop.
你到底还想要什么
Tell me what you need.
分居只是让我理清了一些事情
Our time apart has only clarified things for me.
让我认识了马特 让他走进我的生活
It's allowed me to make room in my life for Matt.
我们打算住在一起了
We're going to be living together now and...
马特 你说的是哪个西尔斯百货的销售员 住我家
Matt, the Sears guy you were talking about, at my house?
马特是业务经理
Matt is an operational manager.
西尔斯百货的
At Sears.
对 你知道的
Yeah, and you know what,
他在工作上的表现也很出色
he gets straight 'A's at his job, too.
但他也很着家
But at home, he's present.
不像你 他一直都在 陪着我们
Unlike you, he's always here for both of us.
他是不是开着一辆绿色普锐斯
Does he drive a green Prius?
如果你要我辞职 我会辞职的
You want me to quit my job, I'll do it.
我会辞掉工作
I'll quit my job.
我不想你为了我辞掉工作
I don't want you to quit for me.
我不会为了你辞职
I wouldn't be quitting for you.
我是辞职是因为你 但是是为了扎克
I'd be quitting because of you for Zach,
所以他没有开着一辆绿色普锐斯
so he isn't driving around Queens
在皇后区里转悠
in a green goddamn Prius.
古德温泽博士
Dr. Goodweather.
太迟了 伊弗
It's too late, Eph.
我爱你但是
I love you but...
你还爱着我的话 又怎么会太迟呢
How can you love me and it be too late?
你要一个疼爱扎克的人
You want a guy who's crazy about Zach?
我是
Check.
一个疼爱你的人
A guy who's crazy about you?
我是
Check.
正派得体 有正当工作
Decent, employed.
是 我都是
Check, check.
你还不懂这就是问题所在吗 伊弗
Can't you see that this is the problem, Eph?
这就是你
This is who you are.
去吧
Go.
诺拉 情况有多糟
Nora, how bad is it?
糟爆了
It's crazy.
差不多有12个不同机构的官员
I have like 12 different agency officials
抢着要负责这里
about to have a dick-measuring contest here.
不行
No.
这是从柏林出发的国际航班
It's an international flight docking out of Berlin.
疾控中心最先收到通知
CDC gets the first call.
我20分钟内会到那里
I can be there in 20 minutes.
这段时间内你能拖延一下检测工作吗
Can you keep the measuring contest going that long?
放心 我会让他们看看我的厉害
Don't worry, I'll show them mine.
可能奏效吧
It might just work.
抱歉
Sorry.
我猜抄表员不明白这是有多急
I guess the meter reader didn't see it as much of an emergency.
马特 是吗
Matt, huh?
是的 我是
Yeah, that's me.
有意思
Interesting.
很遗憾我现在有急事 马特
You know, it's too bad I'm such a rush, Matt.
但我可以肯定会在我家再见到你的
But I'm sure I'll see you again in my house.
开车小心
You drive safe now, you hear?
F滑行道
嘿 老大
Hey, boss.
我的牛奶呢
Got my milk?
在这
Uh, yeah, here.
国土安全局急着想
Homeland Security is just desperate
启动恐怖警报
to push the button on a terror alert.
他们已经准备登机了
They're ready to get on that plane right now.
金 恐怖分子通常都会坠毁飞机
Jim, terrorists usually crash planes,
不会让飞机着陆并关掉引擎的
not land them and shut them down.
报警的人怎么说
So what are the 911 calls saying?
没人报警
There haven't been any.
没有
None?
恩恩
Uh uh.
古德温泽博士
Dr. Goodweather!
上周我们飞去芝加哥
When we flew to Chicago last week
只不过在停机坪上坐了半个小时
we sat on the tarmac for half an hour.
群众就已经被吓坏了 开始发信息 打电话
People were freaking out, texting, calling.
现在却有200个人静静的坐在上面
There've been 200 people sitting there silently for...
超过一个小时
over an hour now.
飞行员呢
Pilots?
完全没有动静
Absolutely no movement.
你做过红外线生命探测了吗
Have you done heat readings?
机体表层温度太冷了
Surface of the plane's too cold.
像个屏障似的把飞机封锁起来
Blocks it all like a screen.
我们把音频探测仪伸到
We got Delsar mics attached
表层进行探测
to the surface of the plane,
几乎完全没有动静
picked up mostly silence.
几乎
Mostly?
有金属板
Well, cooling pings
受冷收缩的声音
from the sheet metal contracting.
还有就是这个
Oh, and there's this.
你觉得这个是什么
What do you think that is?
某种东西发出的声音
Rustling of some sort.
专家认为是引擎关闭
Our experts think it's the engine shutting down
或者是液体沉降的声音
or liquids settling.
从着陆到引擎关闭是多久的时间
How long between landing and shutdown?
6分钟
Six minutes.
时间太短 不足以让感染通过窗户蔓延
It's too short a window for a contagious event.
所以 我想疾控中心这次应该退居二线
So I think CDC should take a back seat on this one.
我同意
I agree.
是吗
Do you?
当然了 我同意
Absolutely, I do.
你多久会摸一次脸
How often do you touch your face?
什么
What?
一天之内 多久摸一次
In a day, how often?
我不知道 大概一小时一次
I don't know, once an hour?
是每三分钟一次
Every three minutes.
你每五分钟就有一次手口碰触
You have mouth/hand contact every five minutes.
每20分钟会跟其他人碰触一次
You touch somebody else every 20 minutes.
传染病就是这么传染的
That's how contagion works.
你不喜欢恐怖分子
You don't like terrorists?
那试下跟病毒打交道吧
Try negotiating with a virus.
一个病毒只有找到寄主才能存活
A virus exists only to find a carrier and reproduce.
它只会这么做 而且繁殖的很快
That's all it does and it does it quickly.
它可没有政治观
It has no political views,
没有宗教信仰 没有文化障碍
it has no religious beliefs, it has no cultural hang-ups.
它不鸟你们的军衔职位
And it has no respect for a badge.
也没有时间和地理的概念
It has no concept of time or geography.
它也许来自中世纪
It might as well be the Middle Ages,
随便搭个时间的便车
except for the convenience of hitching a ride
就能在不同时代中穿梭 进行着一场又一场的杀戮
on a metal tube flying from meal to meal to meal.
瘟疫就是着这样暴发的
That's how a plague begins.
你还想第一个进入机舱吗
So you still want to be the first one through the door?
曼哈顿 哈姆莱区 东118街
我们听说你买银器不要收据 老兄
So we heard you buy silver without a receipt, man.
是这样吗
Is that right?
好银器我永远都要 是的
I'm always in need of good silver, yes.
好吧 那么
Okay, well...
这玩意儿 我能卖个50刀吗
Can I get, uh, 50 for this?
这确实是一块很不错的表
It's a very nice timepiece, indeed.
表带已经断了
I see that the band links have snapped.
你当时应该很急着把它摘下来吧
You must have been in a hurry taking it off.
那它能卖50刀么
Can I... can I get 50 for it?
我只能给你25刀
I can offer you maybe 25...
如果检查没有问题的话
if the test is good.
很不幸呀 只是表面镀了银的黄铜
Unfortunately, this is merely silver-plated brass.
是东欧的伪劣仿制品
A cheap Eastern European knock-off.
啊
Agh!
给我听好了 小子
Listen very carefully, son!
我知道你的小伙伴那儿有枪
I know your little friend has a gun
可能还上了膛 但我不在乎
and the hammer is cocked but I don't care.
我压住你这个穴位就能控制你整个人
I can control your entire body weight from this pressure point
而且我的这把刀直指你的桡动脉
and this knife is pointing straight at your radial artery.
一旦他掏出枪
By the time he clears his coat pocket,
我就一刀下去 从头到尾
your artery will be punctured and sliced wide open
切开你的动脉
from top to bottom.
你会倒在血泊里 我会躲到柜台底下
You fall down bleeding, I go under the counter
你的小伙伴只能对着空气乱射
and your friend starts shooting at an empty space.
我可以向你保证
I can guarantee you this...
911接到报警电话之前 你就会失血而死
you will bleed out before the 911 operator answers the phone.
这是选项一
That is option one!
还有选项二 你把钱放下
Option two is, you release the bills,
你的小伙伴把枪给我
your friend gives me the gun,
他可以留下子弹 我不在乎
he can keep the bullets, I don't care,
然后你们滚出我的店
and you leave this store.
好了 孩子 你选吧
Now, son, you have a choice.
先生们 今晚还需要我为你们效劳些什么吗
Is there anything else I can do for you gentlemen this evening?
今晚发生在肯尼迪国际机场的事件
We have more now on the developing story
又有了新进展
out of JFK Airport tonight.
您现在收看的是现场直播
You're looking at live video
这架飞机是属于里吉斯航空公司的宽体客机
of the airplane identified as a Regis Air widebody jet.
它从柏林起飞
It originated in Berlin
降落之后不久 就熄火了
and it shut down just moments after landing.
据我们所知 飞行员没有发出任何信号
We are told there has been no communication from the pilot.
与机组人员取得联络的一切努力
All attempts to contact the flight crew...
柏林
Berlin...
他又回来了
He's back.
我 呃
I, uh...
我不知道我还有没有当初的力量
I don't know if I have the strength
重新再来一次
to do it all over again.
这一次
This time...
我决不能失败
I cannot fail.
你饿了吗
Feeling hungry?
享用吧 亲爱的
Enjoy, dear.
肯尼迪机场修护 停机坪
一会儿我们要面对的情况 可能会很糟糕
I'm not looking forward to what we'll see out there.
你在听吗
You with me?
停机坪上有架死气沉沉的大客机 还不够刺激吗
Mysterious dead plane on the tarmac not exciting enough?
不好意思 刚从法院安排的
Sorry, just another court-mandated,
离婚家庭心理治疗回来
happy family therapy day.
我注意到了 你还去理了发
I noticed, you cut your hair.
你还穿得整整齐齐
You cleaned up nicely.
戴领带了吗
Did you break out a tie?
在我外套口袋里
It's in my jacket pocket.
心理治疗有效果吗
Did it help?
额 其实没有
Uh, no, in fact, it didn't.
她想带走扎克
She wants to take Zack away from me.
而且还有个毛都没长全的家伙
And there's a... man-child
住在我家里 和我儿子一起
living in my house with my son.
小心
Careful.
专心点
Stay focused.
你和凯莉已经分居一年了
You and Kelly have been separated for a year,
这种情况很正常
and things happen.
我们不也是这样么
It happened to us.
噢 不一样
Oh, that's different.
这怎么不一样了
How is it different?
就不一样
It just is.
我觉得凯莉不会同意我们俩
I don't think Kelly would agree.
她不知道 我从没跟她说过
She doesn't know. I never told her.
你没说过
You didn't?
没有 她
No, she...
她提了离婚 所以我没告诉她
she filed so I didn't tell her.
她不知道
She doesn't know.
你真的一点都不了解女人
You really know nothing about women, do you?
好了 老大
Okay, boss...
准备好进去了吗
ready to go through the looking glass?
准备好了 金
Ready, Jim.
我拿好你的牛奶了
I got your milk.
让它凉着 等我回来
Keep it cold 'til I come back.
哦我的天呐
Oh my God...
金 你看到了吗
Jim, do you see this?
所有乘客 所有人都还在飞机上
It's every passenger. Everyone on the plane.
是的
Yeah.
我们正在看
We're seeing it.
他们都死了
They're all dead.
到底是什么 艾弗 是什么要了他们的命
What is it, Eph? What killed them?
没有挣扎的痕迹
No signs of struggle.
皮肤上没有水疱 没有化学药剂的痕迹
No signs of blistering or chemical agents.
没有淤青
No bruising.
也没有可见的变色
Not seeing discoloration...
没有痕迹
no markings.
妈蛋 到底是什么
Shit, what is it?
瞬间致命 毫无痛楚
Something sudden, painless.
所有的遮光板都关着 除了这一扇
All the window shades are closed except for this one.
是气体泄漏吗 是化学毒气吗
Is it a gas leak? Is it chemical?
探测器检测到了高浓度的氨
The Hazmat Cat's picking up high levels of ammonia.
但还不足以致命
Nothing deadly, though.
飞机的系统不可能出现氨
There shouldn't be any ammonia in the plane systems.
金 查一下货仓的运单
Jim, check the cargo manifest.
明白
Got it.
我要一份货仓运单
I need a cargo manifest.
盖革计数器有反应吗
What about the Geiger?
没有反应  金
It's negative, Jim.
没有可见的创伤
No visible signs of trauma.
没有肿胀
No bloating.
舌头和软腭颜色暗淡 几乎发白
Tongue and soft palate appear pale, almost white.
眼球很清澈
Eyes are clear.
皮肤干燥 没有弹性
The skin is dry, it's inelastic.
没有起泡 没有鼻血
There's no frothing or nosebleeds.
没有挣扎的痕迹
There's no signs of struggle.
非常平静
Almost peaceful.
我们试试紫外照射
Let's try the UV lights.
我的天呐 什么东西
My God, what is this?
你们看到了吗
Are you getting this?
到处都是这些痕迹
These patterns are everywhere.
整个机舱都是
All over the cabin.
只有紫外照射下才看得见
They're only visible under UV light.
这些是生物体的痕迹
The pattern is biological.
可能是氨的来源
Probably where the ammonia is coming from.
我来采样
I'm taking samples.
你来采前舱的 我采后舱的
You take the front galley, I'll take the rear.
吉宝
Jimbo...
这是什么
what is this?
请别叫我吉宝好吗
No, "Jimbo, please"?
额 这是货仓区
Um, that's the cargo compartment.
把它清空
Have it emptied.
把每一件行李都带回去
Take each piece of luggage
进行生物检测和氨谱检测
and check it for biological agents and ammonia spectrum.
了解
Got it.
金
Jim...
驾驶舱门开了
the cockpit door just opened.
它应该是关着的
It should be locked.
诺拉 那扇门不应该是开着的
Nora, that door's not supposed to be open.
我就进去看一眼
Just going to take a quick look.
好了 我要你立刻离开驾驶舱 听到了吗
Alright, I want you back out of there right now, okay?
那扇门应该是锁上的
That door is supposed to be locked.
你不能一个人进去
You shouldn't be in there alone.
诺拉 你听到了吗
Nora, can you hear me?
艾弗
Eph!
驾驶舱的门开着
The door to the cockpit is open.
诺拉在里面
Nora is inside.
诺拉 艾弗
Nora? Eph?
拜托啊同志们 回答我啊
Come on, guys, somebody talk to me!
诺拉 我过来了
Nora, I'm coming!
救救我
Help me!
女士 别拿灯照我脸
Lady, get the light outta my face.
我要让特种部队进来了
I'm sending in SWAT!
别 金 让医疗队进来
No, Jim, send paramedics!
发现幸存者了
We've got survivors!
石心集团
曼哈顿57街 西156号
帕尔默先生
Mr. Palmer...
嘘 他正在做血液透析
Shh! It's his dialysis session.
他睡着了
He's asleep.
那就把他叫醒
Well, then wake him up.
等他透析结束吧
When he's ready.
现在就叫醒
Now.
时间到
In time.
透析完毕
Dialysis complete.
你为石心集团效力多久了 菲茨威廉先生
How long have you worked for Stoneheart, Mr. Fitzwilliam?
毕生效力 先生
All my life, sir.
我父亲去世之后
Mr. Palmer aided me and my brothers
是帕尔默先生帮助了我和我弟弟
after my father passed.
感恩 真是一种有效的契约
Gratitude, what an effective leash.
艾霍斯特先生
Herr Eichhorst...
帕尔默先生 艾霍斯特先生来探望您了
Mr. Palmer, Herr Eichhorst is here to pay his respects.
如果您有需要的话 我就在门外
I'll be outside if you need me.
你可能注意到了这儿有点冷 艾霍斯特
You may notice how chilly it has gotten in here, Eichhorst.
比大楼里的其他地方 都要低20度
Twenty full degrees cooler than the rest of the building.
不过对你来说不算冷 我相信
But not too cold for you, I trust.
当然 你根本不会觉得冷 是吧
Of course, it can't be too cold for you, can it?
货物已经安全抵达
The cargo has arrived safely
四个幸存者也被找到了
and all four survivors have been found.
我这辈子
Throughout my life
已经学会了越界行事
I've learned what it feels to cross a line,
是什么感觉
to do things.
那些不可回头之事
Things that cannot be undone.
那条界
That line...
已经越过了 是吗
it has been crossed now, hasn't it?
我一直不能习惯
Your breath...
没有呼吸的你
I'll never get used to...
是的 即使是我自己都会怀念呼吸的感觉
Yes, even I miss breathing sometimes.
他到了
Here we go.
交给我吧 很快的
Leave it to me, it won't be long.
艾弗雷特
Everett.
艾弗
Eph.
情况有多糟
How bad is it?
国家运输安全委员会接管了布朗克斯区的
The NTSB has taken over a refrigerated chemical warehouse
一间化学药剂冷藏库
in the Bronx.
并把它改造成了巨大的停尸房
They've turned it into a fully contained mass casualty morgue.
没有必要捂这口鼻 艾弗雷特
That's not necessary, Everett.
这些尸体袋经过了三层密封
These bags are triple-sealed.
我要把12具尸体移交给医学继续教育机构
I'm handing a dozen bodies over to the CME
机舱三个部位各取四具
four from each section of the plane
请他们做尸检
for autopsies.
四个幸存者怎么样了
And the four survivors?
我在本地医院安排了隔离病房
I've secured the isolation rooms at a local hospital.
我们要立刻把他们送过去
We need to move them there right away.
他们当然会好好配合的
Of course. I'm sure they'll comply.
配合 我不用要求他们配合
Comply? I'm not asking them.
根据健康权力法案 他们必须隔离
Invoking the Health Powers Act, those four survivors stay.
隔离
Quarantine?
这在疾控中心的权力范围之内的 艾弗雷特 你是知道的
It's within the powers of the CDC, Everett, you know that.
听着 如果你要进行隔离
Look, if you quarantine
我需要你和他们家属会面
I need you to meet with the next of kin.
让他们放心 告诉他们疾控中心正在处理
Reassure them the CDC's on the case.
好吧
Fine.
我们正在想办法弄清
We're trying to figure out what happened,
事情的来龙去脉
what caused this.
-难道这不是最重要的事情吗 -是的当然
- Isn't that what's most important? - Yes, of course.
但防止大规模恐慌 也很重要
But it's also important we don't have full-tilt panic.
这些人需要专家向他们解释
These people need to hear from someone in the field.
我们什么都还没搞清楚
We don't know anything yet.
你们俩好好商量 我没空管这种破事儿
You two figure this out. I don't have time for this shit.
-金 -好
- Jim? - Yeah.
他会见家属的时候
When he talks to the families,
我不想媒体在场 艾弗雷特
I want no press, Everett.
不会有媒体 我保证
No press, I promise.
好吧 你说只有四个人
Okay, you're telling me only four people
在空难中生还
survived this plane crash?
卢斯小姐
Ms. Luss...
是卢斯夫人
It Mrs. Luss.
卢斯夫人 不是空难
Mrs. Luss, there was no crash.
一种不明化学药物
An unidentified agent
杀死了其他所有乘客
killed all of the remaining passengers.
你能提供的任何信息 都会非常有帮助
Any information you can give us would be of great help.
对谁非常有帮助
Of great help to who?
对我们 夫人 疾控中心
To us, ma'am, the CDC.
好吧 我可不是普通的乘客
Okay, well, I'm no ordinary passenger.
我是琼·卢斯
I'm Joan Luss.
我是马特罗夫·卢斯·海恩公司的合伙律师
I'm an attorney... of Matloff, Luss and Hayum.
所以你搜集到的一切信息
So all that information that you're collecting
都要给我一份
you're going to need to get to me.
就个人来说...
Personally...
你在做什么
What are you doing?
别把我封进来 我在和你说话
Don't seal me in, I'm talking to you.
不好意思 小女士 你不许走
Excuse me, little miss. Don't you walk away from me.
我可是琼·卢斯
I am Joan Luss.
雷德芬机长 这是我的同事 马丁内斯博士
Captain Redfern, this is my colleague, Dr. Martinez.
我的飞机怎么了
What happened on my plane?
我们正是想来问你
That's what we came to ask you.
我要你尽力回忆一下
Now, I want you to try to recall, as best you can...
刚割的草 大蒜 青苹果
fresh cut grass, garlic, green apple...
你记不记得昏迷之前
do you remember smelling any of these odors
闻到过这些味道
before you passed out?
啥 草 苹果
What? Grass? Apples?
气味特征 这是大脑记住某种气味的方式
Mnemonic odors, the way our brain reads chemicals.
磷化氢气体 无色 有大蒜气味
Phosphine gas, colorless, smells like garlic.
剧毒的碳酰氯气体 刚割下的草的气味
Or phosgene very toxic, smells like freshly cut grass.
我记得我把飞机降落
I remember landing the plane
转到滑行跑道上
and turning onto the taxiway.
然后
And then...
我就什么都不记得了
I don't remember anything else.
艾弗 你能过来一下吗
Eph, can I get you for a sec?
哦谢天谢地 你来了
Oh, thank God, you're here.
我刚跟他说
I was just telling him
我脑子里面
I have this noise in my head
有嗡嗡嗡的声音
like a hum.
你能再请人过来检查一下我耳朵吗
Could you have someone look at my ears again?
我们会给你做全面检查
We'll have somebody perform a full battery of tests.
不过现在 请你待在棚子里别出来 巴伯尔先生
But for now you need to stay inside this tent, Mr. Barbour.
你不明白
You don't understand.
如果我不打电话回家 我老婆会发疯的
My wife is gonna panic if I don't call soon.
我要打个电话回家
I need to call home.
嘿 就是你
Hey, you.
你是管事儿的吗
You're the guy I gotta talk to around here?
额 我想是的
Uh, yeah, I think so.
给我点止痛药怎么样 医生
How about some Demerol, Doc, huh?
还有 餐车什么时候过来
And what time's that refreshment cart swing by, uh?
玻利瓦尔先生 在飞机降落前
Mr. Bolivar, what is the last thing you can remember
你能记得的最后一件事是什么
before landing?
不知道 呃
I don't know, uh...
好像是一闪一闪的灯光吧
flickering lights, maybe.
我有时候会昏过去
I blackout sometimes.
你手上的这些疤
Those cuts on your arm?
哦 这些啊
Oh, these?
是我自己割的
Yeah, I cut.
为了我的歌迷
For the fans.
告诉我 这些纹身 神神秘秘的图案
Tell me, these tattoos, occult, satanic things
真的是你信仰的一部分么
is this really part of your belief system?
你在开玩笑吧医生
You're kidding, Doc?
我老爸是浸信会的牧师
My father's a Baptist minister.
我这些都是为了把妹
I'm in it for the pussy.
艾弗
Eph.
货仓去的东西你必须去看看
There's something you have to see in the cargo area,
快
right now.
好 走吧
Okay, let's go.
谁把它弄出来的
Who un-crated this thing?
没人
No one.
一来就是这样
This was how it came out.
没有绳子捆绑固定
No straps, no containment wrap.
那这是什么
Well, what is it?
里面装的什么
What's inside of it?
还没人打开呢
No one's opened it yet.
那货单上怎么写的
But, what does it say in the manifest?
货单上没有
It's not on the manifest.
上面只写了高尔夫球棍 橡皮船 机器零件
You got golf clubs, kayaks, machine parts
四十台发动机 一万个套套
40 generators, 10,000 condoms
十个等离子电视 没有说到这个大箱子
10 plasma TVs, but no box.
这是个棺材吧 是不
Looks like a coffin, doesn't it?
棺材吗 这可有九英尺高
Coffin? It's nine feet tall.
很古老
It's old.
且是手工的 不是机器雕刻的
It's hand carved, it's not machined.
大家快过来
Hey, guys, over here.
各位 我们取了样 用盖格仪器测试了
Guys, look, we swabbed it, we ran the Geiger,
发现空气等一切都正常
we did samples of the air and everything is fine.
但航空局很明显
But the NTSB was crystal clear
不想我们碰任何东西
they didn't want us to touch anything.
帮我打开它
Help me open it.
好的
Okay.
土
Soil.
为什么要运一盒子的土
Why would someone ship a box of soil?
又有多少人能够悄无声息的
What are the chances of someone loading this
躲过检查和记录把一盒子土运上飞机呢
unchecked and unlisted?
就这么大的盒子 且在美国的飞机上吗
Something this size in a flight bound for the US?
不可能
Impossible.
至少现如今是不可能
Not in today's world.
金 从上中下部分都取样
Jim, get samples from the top, mid, bottom
用塑料袋封好
plastic seal it.
别让人靠近
No one goes near this,
关税局的 国土安全局的 都不准靠近
not Customs, not Homeland Security, nobody.
伊弗 你看
Eph, look.
是个门栓
It's a latch.
为什么要在里面安门栓
Why would anyone put a latch on the inside?
打给柏林一方
Call Berlin.
这肯定有记录
There's gotta be a record of this.
肯定有人把这玩意儿放上飞机
Somebody put this on the plane.
我们必须找到是谁干的
We just have to find out who.
今晚的肯尼迪机场
A lot of confusion here tonight
疑点重重 内斯特
at JFK International Airport, Nestor.
疾病控制中心的官员
Officials with the Centers for Disease Control...
任何一个不珍惜你妈妈的男人
Any man who doesn't put your mom first
都肯定是疯了 对不对 小扎
is out-of-his-mind crazy. Right, Z?
大量的伤亡
... multiple casualties,
再次强调 在失速的里吉斯753航班
I repeat, multiple casualties
上出现了大量的人员伤亡
aboard the stalled airliner, Regis Air flight 753.
今晚对你来说是一大步
Tonight was a big step for you.
嘘
Shh!
到底是什么导致了这些伤亡
... what caused the fatalities.
如你所见 在我后面
As you can see, behind me
是正在现场的疾病控制中心的官员
officials with the CDC are on the scene.
但不管这是不是
But whether this is any
意味着这是一次生化污染
indication of a biological contamination...
恐怖分子 一定的
Terrorists, it has to be.
小扎 你怎么看
What do you think, Z?
不管是什么 我爸爸都能够处理的
Whatever it is, my Dad will handle it.
晚安
Good night.
晚安 宝贝
Good night, sweetheart.
是什么导致了伤亡
... what caused the fatalities...
你还好吗 爸爸
给我一份有机上乘客登机点
And I need the master list of passengers
的总名单
with their points of embarkation.
还有这班飞机经停的地方
Also every place where that plane landed.
你还好吗 爸爸 我很担心 小扎
今晚很忙 小伙子快睡  明天打电话给你 爱你 爸爸
伊弗
Eph...
家属们都在外面等着呢
the families are waiting.
你知道这么做 就是为了保全他的面子吧
You know this is all about him covering his own ass, right?
你想怎么说就怎么说
Just talk to them like you'd like to be talked to.
说你自己所想
Tell them what you'd like to hear.
不管发生什么我都支持你
Whatever happens I'll be there.
我不知道 是个箱子 但是
这个箱子有点不正常
回电话给我
听着
我不管这里或是柏林是几点
你都要回电话 明白吗
你听到了吗
Hey, you hear that?
没有啊 没听到
No. Sorry, nothing.
搞什么
What the... ?
啊
Agghh!
宝刀未老
Gun hands won't work.
即使关在牢里我也天天找人练手
Knocking boys out every day when I was locked up.
我也要像梅威瑟一样崛起
Raised all the time like Mayweather.
等我成职业选手了
When I go a pro
等我发大财了 我就让你给我洗车
and I get rich rich, I'll let you wash my car.
让他给我当司机
I'll let him be my driver.
哇
Wooo!
然后就可以了 你能睡上一整周
That was it, you gonna sleep for a week.
一直被模仿 有没有 从未被超越
Greatest of all time, baby, greatest of all time.
你在躲我 格斯
You are avoiding me, Gus.
这小子
This guy...
就这样出现了
Just like that?
就这样凭空出现了
Just appear out of nowhere?
让我想到了我前任 有没有
Reminds me of my ex, huh?
我就是这样说她的
Now I'm gonna tell you like I told her,
你怎么找到我的 贱人
how you find me, bitch?
我待会儿再去找你 哥们
I'll catch up to you in a little bit, man.
没事的
We good.
怎样
Wassup?
正如我们谈好的
As we agreed
你到机场去取车
you will pick up the vehicle at the airport.
机场
The airport?
整个机场都被封锁了
The whole place is on lock.
你都不看新闻的吗 小白脸
You don't watch the news, white boy?
你从楼梯过去
You will enter through a service staircase
直接去取车
get the vehicle.
当你过关卡时
When you get to a barricade
他们会放你过去的
you will be let through.
一切都安排好了
It's all arranged.
It's all arranged?
淡定啊 007
Calm down, double o seven.
我可没让你失望过
I never let you down before.
这次不一样
This is different.
我得确定
I need to make sure
你每一步都按照我的指示去做
you follow my instructions precisely.
我这儿有你哥哥的犯罪记录
Your brother's criminal record
还有你妈妈的移民身份证明
and your mother's immigration status.
如果你是在威胁我的话
If this is a threat
那你就大错特错了
you just made a mistake, puto.
我不是在威胁你 我是在奖励你
It is not a threat. It is more a reward.
剩下的酬劳在杂物箱里
The rest of your fee is in the glove box.
那辆车的导航系统上
Destination is pre-programmed
已经输好了目的地
on the GPS in the vehicle.
如果我开失窃车被逮住了 我就玩完了 老兄
I get picked up driving a stolen van, that's it, bro.
我又会被扔回去蹲牢房的
They gonna send me back to the bull pen.
我不能再坐牢了
I can't go back.
这活儿干不了
Can't do it, man.
不是失窃车
It is not stolen.
你一路会畅通无阻
You will be let through
而且事后
and at the end of it
你妈妈的移民问题就解决了
your mother's immigration status will be fixed.
你哥哥的犯罪记录也一笔勾销
Your brother's criminal record erased.
我干 干完我就金盆洗手
I do this for you, that's it, I'm done.
删了我的电话号码和地址
Lose my number and my address.
我现在得为妈妈做点事儿了
I'm trying to do the right thing by my mother now.
如果她发生了什么事
'Cause if anything happens to her
哪怕一点点小事
I mean, anything...
我就废了你
I'll kill your waxy ass.
三个规矩
Three rules...
不许偷看货物
you will not examine the cargo.
中途不许停车
You will not make any stops.
最后是你必须在黎明前
And you will cross the bridge
开过桥回到曼哈顿
back into Manhattan before daybreak.
懂了吗
Do you understand?
你清楚复述一遍 三条规定
In English then, the three rules.
去你的
Screw you.
吃屎吧
Suck my dick.
任务妥妥完成
I'll get it done.
肯尼迪机场 4号航站楼
我女儿在那班飞机上
My daughter was on that flight!
玻利瓦尔 玻利瓦尔 玻利瓦尔
Bolivar! Bolivar! Bolivar!
先生 机场的这部分区域已经封锁了
Sir, this area of the airport is closed.
你得和其他人一样在这里等着
You have to wait back there with everybody else.
嘿 安静点 行不行
Hey, settle down, will ya!
玻利瓦尔 玻利瓦尔 玻利瓦尔
Bolivar! Bolivar! Bolivar!
嘿 先生 先生
Hey, sir! Sir!
先生
Sir!
没事 麻烦去找个轮椅
It's alright, sorry, just go get a wheelchair.
他是个病人
He's a medical.
你还好吧
You all right?
先生 我看看你都有什么药
Sir, what do you have here?
你有 法华林
You have... Coumadin.
你心脏有问题吗
You got a heart condition?
还好吧
Are you all right?
你是这儿的头吗
Are you in charge?
什么
What?
我得找个人说说那架飞机的事儿
I need to talk to someone about that plane.
头等舱的有几个人我认识
I recognize some of these names in First Class.
不过没什么用
That never helps.
听着 伊弗 你就介绍一下你自己
Look, Eph, just introduce yourself
然后说我们正在着手调查
and tell them we're on it.
你能应付的
You'll do great.
去吧
Go on.
你刚才说没有媒体的时候 我差点就信了
When you said no press, I almost believed you.
我是伊弗雷姆 古德温泽
I'm Ephraim Goodweather.
是纽约疾病控制中心的
I'm the Chief Medical Officer
首席医疗官
for the Centers for Disease Control here in New York.
我受命来此做个自我介绍
I have been asked to introduce myself
并且初步解释一下当前的
and to give you a preliminary update on...
有多少幸存者
How many survivors?
别这样
Please...
别这样 别这样 别这样
Please, please, please...
我知道我在这是应该说点安慰你们的话
I think I'm supposed to stand here and somehow reassure you.
可我说不出
I can't do that.
753号航班上
Two hundred and six passengers
206名乘客遇难
on  Air flight 753 are dead.
我们不知道原因
And we don't know why.
有四名活了下来 我们也不知道为什么
Four passengers survived, and we don't know why.
但作为第一个登上该飞机的人
What I can tell you
我只能告诉你们
having been the first to board the plane
他们都走得很平静
is that they all appeared to have died peacefully
没有承受多大痛苦
without distress.
这也是目前我能给大家的唯一的安慰了
That's the only comfort I can give you at this time.
我知道你们想知道为什么
You want answers
想知道那班飞机上到底发生了什么 我也想知道
real answers to what happened on that plane and so do I.
在我们都有一个满意的答案前我绝不罢休
And I won't quite until we're all satisfied.
我才不管这些大话
I don't care about your promises!
我只想要回我的女儿
I want my daughter back!
你们只会说啊说 你们只会说大话
All you do is talk and talk! That's all you do!
这是我的女儿
This is my daughter.
我的女儿 艾玛
My daughter, Emma!
我要见她 活要见人 死要见尸
And I want to see her again, dead, alive.
我是她的父亲
I'm her father!
你难道自己没有孩子吗
Don't you have children of your own?
你良心被狗吃了吗
Don't you have a heart?
给我48小时 我会查出来的
Forty-eight hours, I'll get your answers.
这是我所能做的
It's the best I can do.
不
No!
首席法医办公室
曼哈顿 东30街
天 古德温泽 你这时候找我干嘛
Jesus! Goodweather, what are you doing to me here?
跟我说说你发现了些什么
Just tell me what you have.
我才开始呢
I'm just getting into it now.
我还没有解剖完呢
I haven't finished cutting all of them yet.
那就跟我说说你已经发现的东西
Just give me anything you can.
好吧 首先是
Okay, top of the charts...
看这里
is here.
你能看到这个吗
Can you see this here?
能 那是什么
Yeah, what is that?
是个切口
It's an incision.
刚好能刺穿颈动脉
Deep enough to puncture one wall of the carotid artery
而又没有弄破颈动脉
without rupturing it.
干净利落 下刀干脆 没有淤青或是伤痕
Razor sharp, clean cut, no bruising, no trauma.
没有任何工具能够做到这样的
There's no instrument that can do that.
总之我是不知道什么东西能做到这个程度 如此精准
Not that I'm aware of, anyway, not with this precision.
还有其他发现吗
Anything else?
这就更有趣了
Gets way more interesting.
其他六具尸体都是这样
A spot check of six other corpses revealed the same thing.
同样的地方 同样的伤痕
The exact same wound, in the exact same place.
你是说
Are you telling me
其他乘客也有这样的切口吗
that the other passengers have the same incision?
也可以说是穿刺
Or puncture.
是的 到目前为止都是这样
Yes, all the ones I've looked at so far.
还有个有趣的反常的地方
There is one more intriguing abnormality.
我不知 这是什么
I don't... what the hell am I looking at?
我们这边看起来是白色的东西
On our screen that looks white.
本来就是乳白色的
Because it is white and opalescent.
血蛋白在分离
Blood proteins are separating.
不 实际上 尸体里根本就没有积血
No, in fact, there's a complete absence of hypostasis.
没有血液沉积
No blood pooling anywhere.
连红血细胞都没有
And an absolute absence of erythrocytes.
如果等我解剖了肝脏以后能获得更多信息
I'll know more once I cut into the liver and kidneys but...
我也不想这么对你
I'm sorry to do this to you
但你得单独做这些分析
but you're gonna have to do the preliminary alone.
这事儿一点也不能透露给媒体
I don't want any of this leaking to the press.
好啊 哥们 但你得欠我个人情了
Okay, buddy, but you'll owe me.
欠你一辈子人情
For the rest of my life.
见鬼
Shit.
伊弗 打扰一下
Eph! I'm sorry but I think
不过你可能想和他谈一谈
you're gonna want to talk to this man.
古德温泽博士 我是亚伯拉罕 塞特拉基安
Dr. Goodweather, my name is Abraham Setrakian.
很高兴认识你
It's very nice to meet you.
我现在没法儿和你谈
I can't talk right now.
伊弗 他说他知道这件事的内幕
Eph, he says he has some insight into the outbreak here.
太好了
Great.
肯特 你能来记一下吗
Mr. Kent, here, can take down your information...
时间宝贵啊 博士
Time is of the essence, Doctor.
确实如此 金
It certainly is. Jim...
伊弗
Eph...
你必须听我说
You have to listen to me.
我以前见过这种疾病
I have seen this disease before.
我应对这种情况
I have faced it before.
你 你必须控制疫情
You... you must contain it.
你以前见过
You've seen it before?
我像你保证我们已经采取了必要的措施
I assure you we're taking every available precaution.
你没有 你也没法儿
You're not. You can't.
而这样正中了他的下怀
And he is counting on that.
他
"He?"
我要是在这儿一次性说完来龙去脉
It is too much to say all at once here
你肯定会觉得我疯了
without sounding crazy.
对 你没疯
No, of course not.
呃 金 我们要去货仓看看
Uh, Jim, we're going to the cargo hold
帮我照看一下这位先生
please take care of this gentleman for me.
谢谢
Thank you.
没关系的
It's okay.
跟我来
Just come with me.
那些尸体
The bodies!
他们没有正常地腐烂掉 是吧
They're not decomposing normally, yes?!
组织都还是柔软的
The tissues are still pliable.
- 你怎么知道 - 诺拉 诺拉
- How do you know that? - Nora, Nora...
听我说
Listen to me now.
失敬了 但我必须得说
What I am about to say I do not say lightly.
那班飞机上的所有乘客
All the passengers on that plane
不论死活
dead and alive...
都必须摧毁
they must be destroyed.
摧毁 好吧
Destroyed? Okay.
把他带走 弟兄们
Here you go, fellas.
感觉好多了
Feel better.
必须把头砍掉
The heads must be severed!
把尸体烧掉 一定要摧毁
The bodies burned, destroyed!
博士 你找到棺材了吗
Doctor, did you find the coffin?
如果棺材还在你手里 那你就还能控制住他
If you have the coffin then you still have him!
亡羊补牢还来得及
It is not too late!
摧毁棺材
Destroy the coffin!
不要让它过河
Do not allow it across the river!
首席法医办公室
曼哈顿 东30街
应古德温泽博士要求
As advised by Doctor Goodweather
我将会在紫外灯下进行尸检
I will examine the body under UV light.
那个老头是怎么知道棺材的事
How did that old man know about the coffin?
你说那个箱子
You mean the cabinet?
他叫它棺材
He called it a coffin.
我知道那个老头叫的是棺材
I know what he called it.
他还叫我们毁了那206个尸体呢
He also told us to destroy 206 bodies.
他还有一把剑
And he had a sword.
诺拉
Nora.
什么
What?
这特么是什么
What the hell is that?
像是一条铁线虫
Looks like a horsehair worm
或者是犬恶丝虫
or a Dirofilaria immitis.
构造很简单 只是胶原蛋白组织
Body is simple. It's just collagen.
消化系统功能已经退化至丧失功能
Degenerate non-functional digestive system.
看这个
Look at that.
真美啊
It's beautiful.
它在找寄主 极为迫切
It's looking for a host, it's desperate.
所以这不是通过空气传播的
So it's not airborne.
这就是载体
That's the carrier.
伊弗 看这些
Eph, look.
泥土
Soil.
嘿
Hey!
那个大箱子在哪儿
Where's that cabinet?
什么箱子
What cabinet?
这里 就这里
There, right there.
倒带
Rewind.
你能放慢一点吗 一帧一帧地放
Can you go slower, frame by frame?
这中间一定有断电或者被剪切了
There must be a gap or a cut.
不 没有剪切过
No, there's not cut.
看时间轴
Watch the time code.
2秒 往前
Two seconds. Go back.
从那儿开始
Start there.
等下 等下
Wait, wait.
就这里
There.
这一坨是什么
What's that distortion?
不知道
I don't know.
它抓住了箱子然后提了
It grabs the box and lifts it off...
起来
up...
那个箱子有500磅重
That box was 500 pounds.
没东西能把它提起来
Nothing could lift it up like that.
那个老头说的 如果棺材还在你手里 那你就还能控制住他
The old man said, "If you have the coffin, you still have him."
他
Him.
这个监控显示就在7分钟前
This footage is only seven minutes old.
那箱子还在机场里面
The box is still in the airport.
肯尼迪机场 公用车库
啊哈
Uh huh.
这特么是什么
What the hell is that?
这群疯子
Crazy ass white boy.
快 快 快接电话
Come on, come on, pick up.
金 你在哪儿
Jim, where are you right now?
在主车库门设卡检查
At the main garage door funnelling traffic out.
停下  停下  禁止所有人出入
Stop it, stop it! Stop everyone.
紧急情况
This is an emergency.
你得封锁机场周边
You need to seal off the perimeter of the airport.
那个盒子
That box...
记得有许多花纹的盒子吗
Remember the box with the markings on it?
记得  记得  柏林那边遗漏的货物
Yeah, yeah, the Berlin cargo omit.
就是那个
That's the one.
现在仔细听我说
Now listen carefully, Jim.
我们得阻止所有能容得下它的车辆
We need to stop all vehicles big enough to hold it.
货车  卡车  都不准通过
No vans, no trucks, nothing.
大型车辆都不行  没有例外
No big vehicles. No exceptions.
安全区域任何大型车辆都不得进出  收到
Okay, no big vehicles in or out of the security zone. Got it.
好了  所有人听好
Right, everybody listen up.
没有我的批准
I want none of these trucks
任何货车及大型车辆都不得放行
big-sized vehicles released without my authorization.
快点
C'mon...
停在那里  先生  我马上过来
Pull up there, sir, I'll be right with you.
操  操  操
Shit! Shit, shit!
身份证和许可证
ID and permit.
好的  伙计
Oh, yeah, man.
真疯狂  发生了什么
Crazy what's happening, huh?
你给我这个是什么意思
What do you want me to do with this?
下车  打开货箱  先生
Step out of the vehicle, open the cargo area, sir.
下车
Step out of the vehicle...
-别拿灯照我的脸  -下车
- Get the light out of my face! - Step out of the vehicle.
能让我先解了安全带吗
Can I get my seatbelt?
嘿 怎么了
Hey. What's going on here?
我要看身份证  他给了我这个
I asked for ID, he gave me this.
这是我们的车
Oh, well, this is one of our vehicles.
-你可以让他过去  -长官
- You can let him through. - Sir?
我说了  让他过去
I said, let him through.
你告诉那些贱货我不干了
You tell those sons of bitches I'm done.
这是我最后一次帮他们
I came through for them but now I am done.
听到没有
You got it?
走吧
Okay, go.
我现在打开其中一具尸体的胸腔
I have now removed the chest plate of one of the subjects
发现
and found...
心脏  肝脏以及肾脏中
abnormal neoplasms in the heart, liver...
都有不寻常的肿瘤
and kidneys.
从生长情况来看不像是癌变体
The growths do not seem like oncological aberrations
更像是具备完整功能的器官
but almost like new, fully functional organs.
天哪
What?!
不要
No!
啊
Ah!
Agh!
对不起  伊弗  没有发现
Sorry, Eph. Nothing.
你这有什么进展吗
You got anything here?
正在想办法搞清楚
Just trying to figure out
一具重达五百磅高九英尺的棺材是怎么被带走的
how a 500-pound, 9-foot tall coffin got up and walked away.
你管那叫棺材
You called it a coffin.
下次运气就不会这么差了
We'll get a break.
每次都是这样
We always do.
现在要做的就是找到切入点
We just gotta find some place to start.
这就是我们的切入点
This is where we start.
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell are those?
新玩意
Something new.
塞-特-拉-基-安
S-e-t-r-a-k-I-a-n?
塞特拉基安
Setrakian?
这是哪国名字
What is... what is that?
亚美尼亚
Armenian.
你是从那来的
Is that where you're from?
曾经是
At one time...
我什么时候可以走
How soon may I leave?
到周一才能立案
Well, nothing happens 'til Monday.
到时候就知道了
The charges are filed then.
现在已经快天亮了
It's almost dawn now.
皇后区 南牙买加 纽约警署113分局
你是图书管理员吗
Are you the librarian?
噢
Oh...
你胳膊上的印记够古老的  老头
That's some ancient ink you got there, old man.
写的什么  数字吗
What is it, numbers?
是的  数字
Yeah, numbers.
有什么意义吗
Mean anything?
只对我有意义
Only to me.
一切都按计划进行
Everything went as planned.
爱会指引他们回家
Love is going to guide them all back
回到心爱的人身边
to their homes, to their loved ones.
有件怪事
Curious detail...
一名携带佩剑的老人在机场被逮捕
an old man with a sword was arrested at the airport.
那个犹太人
The Jew.
他居然还活着
He's still at it.
经过了这么多年
After all these years.
就凭这点你也应该对他表示尊重
You must admire him for that.
我来搞定他
I'll take care of him.
我俯瞰这片岛屿
I look out upon this island
慢慢品味这即将到来的
and I savour what is to come...
纯净
purity.
费茨威廉先生
Mr. Fitzwilliam...
一个多愁善感的人
a sentimental man
会在这一切降临之前
would venture out into the city tonight
深入这座城市
to walk these streets one last time...
将街头巷尾再走一遍
before the fall.
您还有别的吩咐吗  先生
Do you require anything else, sir?
没有了
No.
生平第一次
For the first time in my life
我所需要的都已经拥有了
I have everything I need.
喂
Hello?
嗨 妈咪
你是谁
还能有谁
你在抽烟吗
什么  不  妈妈  我没抽
Huh? No, mommy, no.
我没抽烟  你开玩笑吗
I'm not smoking. You kidding me or what?
我在工作
I'm working.
就是打电话问问你在干什么
Just called to check in to see what you're up to.
克里斯宾在家吗
Is Crispin home?
他在
He is.
至少我能盯着他
妈妈  就剩一罐啤酒了
Mama, one beer left.
你为什么要这样对我
Why do you do this to me?
需要我说多少次
How many times do I gotta tell you?
我在给他做早饭
I'm making his breakfast.
我快到大桥了
I'm getting on the bridge now.
一小时之内到家
I'll be home in an hour.
我爱你
我也爱你 儿子 拜拜
我不知道你是什么  不过你给我带来了好运
I don't know what you are but you're bringing me good luck.
爱是一种无法解释的力量
Love, you see, is the one force that cannot be explained
无法用化学的方式来理解
cannot be broken down into a chemical process.
它是指引我们回家的明灯
It is the beacon that guides us back home
就算没有人在那里
when no one is there
那道光也会照亮前方迷途的路
and the light that illuminates our loss.
爱的缺失会剥夺我们
Its absence robs us of all pleasure
感知快乐的能力
of our capacity for joy.
会让黑夜更加黑暗  白天黯淡无光
It makes our nights darker and our days gloomier.
但当我们找到爱
But when we find love
不管多畸形  多悲伤  多恶劣
no matter how wrong, how sad or how terrible
我们紧紧抓住不放
we cling to it.
爱给我们力量
It gives us our strength.
爱使我们屹立不倒
It holds us upright.
我们以爱为生  爱以我们为生
It feeds on us and we feed on it.
皇后区 牙买加住宅区 都铎路
艾玛  艾玛
Emma... Emma...
爸爸
我冷
我好冷
艾玛
Emma...
宝贝儿
Oh, baby...
你回来了
爱是恩赐
Love is our grace.
爱是陷落
Love is our downfall.
新浪微博@SSK字幕组·合作贴吧《美剧血族》吧
更多精彩内容敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
如果你对这部剧有什么看法请进入百度贴吧《美剧血族》吧